>> Kyle Simpson: 这里是一个长期令人沮丧的地方
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's a place
where it is perpetually frustrating
我们有超载的经营者
that we have overloaded operators.
我们倾向于认为花括号必须是范围。
We tend to think that curly
braces must be scopes.
它们是块体，它们是函数体，它们必须是作用域。
They're blocks, they're function bodies,
they must be scopes.
当我在第 3 行定义一个箭头函数时，会发生什么 ?
What's gonna happen when I define
an arrow function on line three?
>> Kyle Simpson: 该箭头的父词汇作用域是什么
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What is the parent
lexical scope from which that arrow
功能要上一级去解决吗 ?
function will go up one
level to resolve the?
>> 演讲者 2: 全球?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Global?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是全球性的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is the global.
这不是研讨会的对象，因为猜测是什么 ?
It is not the workshop object because,
guess what?
只要把花括号括在那个物体周围，就不可能成为一个范围。
Just cuz there's curly braces around
that object doesn't make it a scope.
对象不是作用域。
Objects are not scopes.
这是一个很常见的错误，人们有，而且有上百个
So this is a very common mistake that
people have, and there's hundreds of
关于 Stack Overflow 的问题，在这个程度上，人们在说，
questions on Stack Overflow to this
extent, where people are saying,
为什么箭头功能不把我的工作室作为我的内容呢 ?
why is the arrow function not
getting my workshop as my content?
因为工作坊对象不是一个范围
Well, because workshop
object's not a scope.
你得想想一个箭的作用
You have to think about an arrow
function as not having of this and
在词法上解决。
resolving it lexically.
那么，父母的范围是什么 ?
So what is the parent scope?
此程序中只有两个作用域。
There's only two scopes in this program.
请求函数的作用域，即箭头和全局作用域。
The scope of the ask function,
which is an arrow, and the global scope.
中间没有介入的范围
There's no intervening scope in between.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 不幸的是，我们已经超载了
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is unfortunate that
we've overloaded the curly brace that
让我们觉得它是一个范围但它不是
confuses us into thinking it's a scope,
but it isn't.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果你把所有的细微差别都用在箭头上
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if you take
all of this nuance around arrow
函数和这些关键字。
functions and these keywords.
如果你考虑到我以前的评论
If you take it into account
with my former comments on,
我认为箭头函数的缺点是箭头函数是匿名的
I think arrow functions, the downside is
that arrow functions are anonymous and
所以他们有时更难有问题他们也不清楚自己的情况
so they're a bit harder to bug at times,
they don't explain themselves well.
如果你把整个环境
If you take the entire context,
我的感觉是你唯一能使用的时候
my perception is that the only time
you should ever use an arrow function
就是当你从词法中获益的时候
is when you're gonna benefit
from lexical this behavior.
因为这个词法的替代方法是一个黑客
Because the alternative to
lexical this behavior is a hack
就像这个人一样
like the var self equals this case.
当然，你们中的一些人看到的代码是你自己做的，
Surely, some of you have seen code
where you did var self equals this and
然后你引用这个细胞
then you reference the cell.
或者，它被称为 var ，或者 var 强调了这个，或者什么。
Or maybe it was called var that or
var underscore this, or whatever.
让我说， var self 等于这是最糟糕的名字
Let me just say, var self equals
this is the worst possible name
任何一个人都能来的
anybody ever could have come up with.
因为这个关键词从来没有，在任何情况下，
Because this keyword never, ever,
ever, under any circumstances,
它指向功能本身，它指向一个上下文。
points at the function itself,
it points at a context.
所以如果你一定要做到这一点
So if you absolutely must do
the var self equal this hack,
请执行代表此操作的 var 上下文。
please do var context equals this.
库兹这个关键词是什么，是一个背景，好吗 ?
Cuz that's what this keyword is,
is a context, okay?
但是这个箭头函数的词法
But this arrow function
lexical this behavior
比一个 " var " 的人更能做到这一点
is a much better way of doing
it than a var self equals this.
我甚至会认为比做功能更有效。
And I would argue even better
than doing the function.bind.
它是一个比较好的方法，因为它实际上匹配了
It is a much better way because it
actually matches the mental model of
我们想要的
what we want.
我们希望此关键字在此处进行词法。
We want the this keyword
to behave lexically here.
我们不希望箭头功能对它有一些神奇的行为。
We don't want for the arrow function to
have some magical this behavior to it.
我们希望它仅采用某个父作用域的此关键字。
We want it to just adopt the this
keyword of some parent scope.
这就是它的目的所以它是正确的工具
And that's what it does, so it is
the right tool designed to fix the right
如果你想正确的话就会有问题
problem, if you're inclined
to think correctly about it.
所以我说，一般来说，不要使用箭功能，如果你是这样的话，就像
So whereas I've said, generally, don't use
arrow functions, if you're in a case, like
几个幻灯片之前是 setTimeout，你在那里合法需要这个词法，
a couple slides ago with the setTimeout,
where you legitimately need lexical this,
请使用箭头功能， cuz 是作业的正确工具。
please use the arrow function,
cuz that's the right tool for the job.
其实我去写的是 ESLint 规则，
As a matter of fact, I went so
far as to write an ESLint rule,
这需要你的箭功能来做这个推荐人
that requires your arrow
functions to make this references,
它不允许任何未使用词法的箭头函数。
it disallows any arrow function
that is not using lexical this.
这很有争议
That's extremely controversial,
我知道，很少有人会使用 ESLint 规则。
I know, unlikely that very many people
are ever gonna use that ESLint rule.
但如果你和我一样认为箭功能有这个目的
But if you, like me, think that arrow
functions have that purpose and
这就是他们应该用的
that's what they ought to be used for,
这是一个插件，它将为您提供控制该行为的规则。
that's a plug-in that will give you
a rule to control that behavior.
问题。
Questions.
嗯。
Yes.
>> 扬声器 3: 仅确认。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Just to confirm.
当我们回到这张幻灯片的时候，当我们正在分析这个问题时，
Going back one slide, so when we’re,
when we would be parsing this,
讲习班将会进入红桶，使全球范围变得越来越大。
workshop is going into the red bucket,
it’s getting the global scope.
不过，教师的财产的范围是 -
The teacher property,
though, would be scoped to-
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 属性未限定范围，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Properties aren't scoped,
属性不是词法标识。
properties aren't lexical identifiers.
>> 演讲者 3: 好的，知道了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay, got you.
>> Kyle Simpson: 它是对象值上的成员。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's
a member on an object value.
>> 演讲者 3: 好的。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 没有参加
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's not participating
在词法范围内
in lexical scope at all.
我唯一的例外是不使用箭头功能因为他们是匿名的
My one and only exception to the don't use
arrow functions because they're anonymous,
当您可以从词法中获益时使用箭头函数。
is use arrow functions when you
can benefit from the lexical this.
不过我会说
I will however say,
如果你要用一支箭式的功能来做你的词法
that if you gonna use an arrow function to
get your lexical this, you need to combat
我们讨论的那三个方面是匿名的
those three downsides that we talked
about with anonymous function.
你需要对抗这种不记名的功能
You need to combat the downside that,
anonymous functions don't
具有自我引用，以防您需要进行递归或取消绑定。
have a self reference, in case you
need to do recursion or unbinding.
你必须对抗他们没有名字的事实
You need to combat the fact
that they don't have a name.
在某种程度上用它来推断出
Use it in some way so that it's
gonna get a name inference, like,
将其分配给变量或属性。
assign it to a variable or a property.
因为它会以匿名形式出现
Because it's gonna show up
as anonymous otherwise.
你需要有一些方法让读者明白清楚。
And you need to have some way of making
it clear and obvious to the reader.
此功能的用途是什么 ?
What is the purpose of this function?
别让他们读函数体来解决这个问题
Don't make them read the function
body to figure that out.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在我们已经谈过这个关键词了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
now we've talked about the this keyword.
我们已经看到了它的不同角度，我很高兴的是
We've seen all of its different angles,
and what I'm thrilled about actually is
对于此关键字，箭头函数不是另一个规则。
that the arrow function is not
a different rule for the this keyword.
我害怕当他们添加箭的功能时我们要修改
I was afraid when they were adding arrow
functions that we were gonna have to amend
这些规则还有第五条规则要保持在我们头上但这不是规则
these rules, and have a fifth rule to keep
floating in our head, but it's not a rule
因为此关键字甚至不适用箭头函数。
at all because the this keyword doesn't
even apply instead of arrow functions.
您唯一需要执行的操作是查找此关键字
The only thing you ever need to do to
understand the this keyword is look for
定义此关键字的函数的调用站点，以及
the call site of a function that
defines the this keyword, and
问这四条规则
ask those four rules.